dollarsurveys.net 2018-12-31

# Paid Online Surveys for Free

### We Respect Your Privacy.

This privacy policy sets out how DollarSurveys.net uses and protects any information that you give DollarSurveys.net when you use this website. 

DollarSurveys.net is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

DollarSurveys.net may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 7/14/2008. 

**What we collect**   
We may collect the following information: 

* Email address   
* Site usage information 

**What we do with the information we gather**   
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

* Internal record keeping.  
* We may use the information to improve our products and services.  
* We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. These emails will be clearly labeled and only sent to you if you have expressly requested to receive our partner bonus mails on our website  
* We may use the information to provide special offers or services to you. In every case, you will be complete control as to whether or not you want to participate in such offers.

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Notwithstanding any other provision, we may also engage a data provider who may collect web log data from you (including IP address and information about your browser or operating system), or place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, that we may share with a data provider solely in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these data provider cookies, please go to <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

**Links to other websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over the content of other websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

* if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us here. You may also automatically opt out  
* We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.  
* You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to  
DollarSurveys.net Privacy  
20 Jay Street, Ste. 502  
Brooklyn, NY 11201

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
